visabillpay.in 2009-06-12

# Visa Bill Pay

|  |   
|  | 

|  | Privacy Policy   
---  
  
****  
  
Any time you visit a Web site, you may be providing information about yourself to the site’s owner or operator. We at Visa Bill Pay respect and value your privacy and safeguarding your information is of utmost importance to us. We believe it is important that you know how we treat the information that we receive on the Internet and that information shared with us is safeguarded in accordance with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality both internally and externally 

At Visa Bill Pay we use information that we get from your visit to enable you to participate in and take advantage of the various programs and features presented on the Visa Bill Pay site and to make the Visa Bill Pay site useful and interesting to you. We do not use the information that we collect from the Visa Bill Pay site for any other purpose, nor do we share it with third party, except as specifically noted and with agencies, vendors, partners, or affiliates under contract with Visa Bill Pay.   
  
****  
Applicability of this Privacy Policy   
****  
  
This Privacy Policy applies only to the information that we collect on the Visa Bill Pay site and not to any information that we collect through other methods or sources, including sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors, or partners. 

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Service.   
  
****  
| ****On this page  
---  
Notice  
****What personal information we collect and how we use it  
****What are cookies and how does Visa Bill Pay use them   
****Sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys   
****Email, mailing lists, and other services   
****Affiliated businesses and links to other sites   
****Our policy regarding selling or renting of personal information   
****Agents   
****Banners and other advertisements on Visa Bill Pay  
****Business transfers   
****Disclosure of personal information for legal purposes and protection of **** **** ****Visa and others  
Choice  
****How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us  
Security  
****How we protect your personal information   
****Security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration      of your information   
Customer service and recourse   
****Changes to the Visa Bill Pay Privacy Policy   
****How to contact Visa Bill Pay regarding your concerns and questions  
  
****  
  
NOTICE  
   
What personal information we collect and how we use it  
****  
When you visit the Visa Bill Pay site, we may capture your Internet provider's domain name (e.g. 'sify.com') and may also capture the route from where the visit came, and the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your "click stream" activity).   
****  
Information we collect on the Visa Bill Pay site may be used to enhance this site in ways like these:   
****  
| 

|  Arrange the Web site in the most user-friendly way   
---|---  
  
|  Customize your browsing experience of this Web site   
  
|  Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices  
  
|  Respond to your question or suggestions  
****  
Visa Bill Pay only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using or registering with the Visa Bill Pay site. "Personal information" includes information that can identify you, such as:   
****  
| 

|  Name, address, phone number, email address, or company name   
---|---  
  
|  Log-in information   
  
|  Bill / Biller information   
  
|  Credit card information   
  
|  IP address (Note: For users who access the Internet from an Internet Service Provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time you log on. Visa Bill Pay does not typically associate this information with any individual.)   
****  
When you register or use Visa Bill Pay services you are required to provide data / information that Visa Bill Pay needs in order to create your Visa Bill Pay account and fulfill our service commitment to you. This is collected on the registration form and from the Biller / bill details provided by you. These details are necessary to service your account. 

While you can browse our site without providing personal information, you will need to input certain personal information as indicated on specific pages of our site in order to take advantage of certain features, such as requesting updates on promotional offers or participating in special programs. 

Like any business interested in attracting and offering the highest quality of service to clients, Visa Bill Pay may, from time to time, send you e-mail and other communication to tell you about Visa Bill Pay’s services, features, functionality and content or seek voluntary information from you. Visa Bill Pay may also on occasion ask you to voluntarily submit information about other people. For example, you might be asked for the name and email address of people you know so we can inform them about a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion or program offered on the Visa Bill Pay site. This information is kept completely private and confidential. It is aggregated with that of all other clients to provide us with the ability to tailor our services and content to those individuals most interested in our service.  

****  
****  
What are cookies and how does Visa Bill Pay use them?   
****  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site if you do so. 

Currently Visa Bill Pay does not use cookies but may do so in the future uses cookies to track user traffic patterns and to help us assist you with questions about site navigation, functionality or performance.   
  
****  
****  
Sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys  
****  
From time to time, Visa Bill Pay may conduct sweepstakes, contests, games or other promotions, and also conduct surveys through the Web site. If you choose to participate—unless otherwise noted in the applicable rules, terms and conditions, or disclaimers—we may use the information you provide in connection with the administration of the applicable promotion, including for selection and notification of sweepstakes or contest winners and for creation of new promotions, and/or to publish survey results in aggregate on the site. 

Promotions that run on Visa Bill Pay may be sponsored or cosponsored by entities / services other than Visa Bill Pay. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared. 

Except where necessary to administer a sweepstakes, contest, game or other promotion, or survey, unless you have otherwise agreed or unless required by law, we will never permanently record or publish any response you give connected to your name or address. We will hold these responses only as anonymous statistics.   

****  
****  
Email, mailing lists, and other services  
****  
When you request information or services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or services you’ve requested, including sending transaction confirmations, acknowledgements and alerts. Mail confirming your transactions or any changes to your account information, will be sent as per Visa Bill Pay’s prevailing operating policy and with a view to enhance the security of the service offering. 

In respect of other information or services sent to your email address, we will continue to provide these until you ask us to stop (by using the “unsubscribe” instructions provided on each email and/or the Web site where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your email address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless the message or information is part of the service you are requesting).   

****  
****  
Affiliated businesses and links to other sites  
****  
We work closely with our affiliated businesses, vendors and partners, many of which may have links within the Visa Bill Pay site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Visa Bill Pay site to another Web site, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. Your browsing and interaction on any third party’s Web site, including any site that has a link on Visa Bill Pay is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to better understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.   
****  
****  
Our policy regarding selling or renting of personal information  
****  
Our policy is simple: we do not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances, except in the event of a bankruptcy or reorganization, or a sale of all or substantially all of our assets, as further provided below.   
****  
****  
Agents  
****  
We may employ other companies and individuals to perform services on behalf of Visa Bill Pay, such as (1) administering special reward or other programs affiliated with Visa Bill Pay, or sweepstakes, contests and other promotions, (2) sending emails, (3) providing marketing assistance, and (4) analyzing data. Such companies and individuals will have access to the personal information necessary to perform their services, but will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose.   
****  
****  
Banners and other advertisements on Visa Bill Pay  
****  
The Visa Bill Pay site may displays banners and other advertisements that may be placed by third parties. Such advertisers may collect non-personal information (meaning, information that is not identifiable to any individual) when you click or scan one of their advertisements, by placing cookies on your computer or by using other technology. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such third parties. In addition, we may share aggregate information about our visitors to third-party ad servers or potential advertisers in order to provide advertisements on Visa Bill Pay about products and services that may be of interest to you.   
****  
****  
Business transfers  
If a third party acquires all or substantially all of our assets, your personal information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected on the Visa Bill Pay site may be transferred to such third party as part of our business assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered one of our assets and may be sold or transferred to third parties.   
****  
****  
Disclosure of personal information for legal purposes and protection of Visa and others  
****  
We reserve the right to share your personal information with third parties if required to do so by law, or if we believe such action is necessary in order to: (a) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served upon us; (b) protect or defend our legal rights or property, the Visa Bill Pay site, or our users; or (c) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of the terms and conditions for using the Visa Bill Pay site.   
****  
****  
CHOICE  
****  
How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us  
****  
If you choose to receive them, we may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this Web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request.   
****  
****  
SECURITY  
****  
How we protect your personal information  
****  
The security of your personal information is very important to us, and we are committed to protecting the information we collect.

Visa Bill Pay will work with your biller institution to present your bills, account balances and history to you on your Visa Bill Pay member pages. In order to present your billing information to you, Visa Bill Pay receives that information from your financial institution and presents it to you over a secure-server. As with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective partners regarding service usage on Visa Bill Pay are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.  
  
****  
****  
Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information  
****  
Your Visa Bill Pay account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. You may edit your Visa Bill Pay account information by using your Visa Bill Pay User ID and password. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Visa Bill Pay has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure all Personal Information that Visa Bill Pay collects online. To learn more about our security click here. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password or your secret question and answer to anyone. Visa Bill Pay will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your Visa Bill Pay account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Visa Bill Pay uses firewalls and Secure Socket Layers for all personal data we collect from you. We also employ many different security techniques to protect personal data against loss, misuse, alteration, and unauthorized access. But we cannot guarantee perfect security of your personal information.   
  
****  
****  
CUSTOMER SERVICE AND RECOURSE  
****  
Changes to the Visa Bill Pay Privacy Policy  
****  
This Privacy Policy was revised and posted on June 15, 2005. Visa Bill Pay reserves the right to change, modify, or amend this policy at any time and post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our Privacy Policy updates. Please also read over the Visa Bill Pay Terms and Conditions.  
****  
****  
How to contact Visa Bill Pay regarding your concerns and  questions  
****  
Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any services related to the Visa Bill Pay site, you consent to let us process this information in India as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. 

If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about Visa Bill Pay’s Privacy Policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to email us at [visabillpay@billdesk.com](mailto:visabillpay@billdesk.com) or write to us at: **** Attention: Customer Care - (Privacy Policy Issues); IndiaIdeas.com Limited, Visa Bill Pay Service, E-510, Crystal Plaza, New Link Road, Andheri (W) Mumbai 400 053  

****  
Additional Information   
****  
If at any time you believe that Visa Bill Pay has not adhered to these privacy guidelines, please notify us by email at [visabillpay@billdesk.com](mailto:visabillpay@billdesk.com) and we will we will resolve it and take any remedial action as we reasonably determine in our discretion and in accordance with applicable laws.
